alldigitalnetwork.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy

All Digital Network respects your privacy and recognizes the need to protect the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We would like to assure you that we follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our web sites. There are times when we may collect personal information from you such as name, physical address or telephone number. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. Generally, you will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to “opt out” of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit the All Digital Network website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services.

All Digital Network – will not sell, trade or disclose to third parties any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service (including names and addresses) without the consent of the user or customer (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the user or others). All Digital Network – will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure.

All Digital Network – will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. If our privacy policy changes in the future, it will be posted here and a new effective date will be shown. You should access our privacy policy regularly to ensure you understand our current policies. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. All Digital Network will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt. Thank you for using All Digital Network. If you have any query/doubts, kindly feel free to drop an E-mail at [contact@alldigitalnetwork.com](mailto:contact@alldigitalnetwork.com).
